filesupload.online 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web site**

Our website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.

**Third party websites and Cookie Policy**

Our website does include links to third party web service providers including **Google AdSense** , **Google Analytics** and other advertising or social media platforms which may use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyses our traffic. We also share non personal information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services. To learn more please check [how Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

**Automatic Collection of Information**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services and filling our forms.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used.

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.

**Confidentiality / Security**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * Unauthorized access

  * Improper use or disclosure

  * Unauthorized modification

  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask by contacting us

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. - although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

  * erased

  * rectified or amended

  * completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
